onemorelesbian.com 2016-11-19

# One More Lesbian | Film, Television and Video On Demand Privacy Policy | One More Lesbian | Film, Television and Video On Demand

Please also visit our[ Terms of Use](http://www.onemorelesbian.com/terms-of-use) section that explains other terms governing the use of our website.

Thank you for accessing the website (the “Site”) of OML MEDIA CORPORATION INC. (“One More Lesbian,” “We” or “Us”). At One More Lesbian, we are committed to protecting the privacy and security of your personal information. To learn more, please read this privacy policy that follows (the “Privacy Policy”).

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information on or through the Site. By visiting this Site, and/or using the services offered on or through this Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time.  As We update and expand our services, this Privacy Policy may change, so check back to this page from time to time.  This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Website [Terms and Conditions](http://www.onemorelesbian.com/terms-of-use), which governs your use of this Site.

This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we may collect, how we may use this information and when (under certain circumstances) we may disclose this information. This Privacy Policy also details the steps we have taken to secure your personal information.

This Privacy Policy only applies to information that you may provide to Us, or that we may obtain, through your use of this Site.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**  
As you interact with us by using our Site, We may ask you to provide us with certain personal information that is necessary for us to enhance and personalize our services and marketing efforts. We define personal information as information about you that enables us to identify or contact you, including but not limited to your name, mailing or postal address, telephone number, email address, payment method (such as credit card, debit card, or other payment methods accepted by Us) as well as other information we maintain about you, such as your account history, financial information, content viewed and/or ordered or category of content viewed and/or ordered. Examples of ways in which we may collect such information from you include the following:

**A. Registration and Ordering.** Before using certain parts of this Site or ordering content under OML PLUS, you are required to complete a registration form. When registering, you will be prompted to provide certain personal information, including but not limited to your name, billing addresses, phone number, email address, and credit card number. In addition, you may also be asked to provide your country of residence and/or your organization’s country of operation and your age, so we can comply with applicable laws and regulations. These kinds of personal information are used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and this Site, and for internal marketing purposes. If we encounter a problem when processing your order, we will use the personal information to contact you.

**B. Email Addresses.** Some areas of the Site allow you to enter your email address for purposes including, but not limited to: registering to use our services or for our on-line newsletter.

**C. Cookies & Other Technologies.** Like most other websites, We use cookie technology throughout this Site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your system for record keeping purposes. In general, cookies can make the Internet more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular system. Unfortunately, viewers who turn off cookies in their browser settings will not be able to use or view content on our Site. THIS SITE’S COOKIES DO NOT AND CANNOT INFILTRATE A USER’S HARD DRIVE TO GATHER A USER’S CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION. Our cookies are not “spyware.”

Some of our business partners, such as our advertising partners, use cookies on our Site. Please be advised that w have no access or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies.

In addition to cookies, we also use a variety of other technologies, including pixel tags (web beacons) and clear gifs to gather information on how users interact with our service. These technologies can help personalize the service for you and help associate your interactions with our service to other information within your account. They can show us, for example, popular pages, conversion rates, viewing patterns, click-through and other information that can be used to improve, operate and monitor our Site and other aspects of our service.

**INFORMATION USE**  
We do not sell or rent information about our viewers and all information provided to Us remains absolutely confidential, except that:

A) We may share aggregate or summary information regarding our viewers with partners, advertisers or other third parties. This data will never identify you personally.  
B) We may share information with companies that provide support services to us (such as web hosting) or that help us market our business and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose.  
C) We will use your personal information to communicate with you about your orders, and we may send you a confirmation email when you register/place an order with us. Also, if you submit your email address to register for our OML PLUS or our Newsletter, we use it to deliver the information to you.  
D) We may be required to disclose such information in response to subpoenas, court orders, requests from law-enforcement officials, or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law.  
E) We may publicly disclose the name, city, and state of the winner of any online sweepstakes.

**PROTECTING YOUR INFORMATION**  
While We will take reasonable precautions to protect the security and integrity of your personal information provided to our Site, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, We cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.  Unfortunately, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. With that in mind, We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information.

For example:

We use industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) authentication for online transactions made on our Site. SSL authentication and encryption of the information that you send to Us over the Internet helps protect your online transaction information from third party interception.

Your credit card information is never used except charges for orders placed on our Site.  For your own safety, please don’t ever use email to send us your credit card information!

We never display your full credit card number once it has been entered. We will only reveal the last four digits of your credit card for verification purposes.

For additional security, we do not store your credit card number after processing your payment.

While we do our best to protect your privacy, we urge you to also protect your own privacy. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone or share your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail.

In addition, while using our services, you will have the opportunity to post reviews or other personal information in the public forums available on our Site. When you post such information, it is made public and therefore such disclosure is not subject to this privacy policy. You hereby agree and understand that One More Lesbian is not responsible for any third party’s use of any personal information you publicly disclose through our services on our Site.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**  
Please note that you must be at least 18 years of age to access our Site. In certain jurisdictions, the age of majority may be older than 18, in which case you must satisfy that age in order to use our Services. While individuals under the age of 18 may utilize the service, they may do so only with the involvement, supervision, and approval of a parent or legal guardian, and subject to our [Terms of Use](http://www.onemorelesbian.com/terms-of-use). We are committed to protecting children’s privacy on the Internet and we comply fully with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If we become aware that we have collected personally identifiable information from a user of the Site who is under the age of thirteen, we will remove that child’s personal information from our files.

**OPT OUT / CORRECTIONS**  
Upon your request, we will (a) correct or update your personal information; (b) stop sending emails to your email address; and/or (c) disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account. You can make these requests by emailing your request to Our Customer Support department at [info@onemorelesbian.com](mailto:info@onemorelesbian.com). Please clearly label the subject line “Opt Out / Corrections,” and do not email your credit-card number or other sensitive information.

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**  
This privacy policy applies only to information collected by Us. However, our Site contains links to other websites owned and operated by third parties who may treat the collection, use and disclosure of personal information differently than we do. While we strive to associate with reputable websites, One More Lesbian shall not be not responsible for data collection, use and disclosure practices of other third parties which our Site may provide links to. We recommend that you be aware when you leave our Site and make sure to read the privacy statements of such third parties.

**CONSENT TO PROCESSING**  
By providing your personal information to this Site, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information within the United States.

**POLICY CHANGES**  
We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of this Site by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page.  Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this Site and shall supersede any prior policy.  Under certain circumstances, We may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by other means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our Site or by sending you an e-mail.

**QUESTIONS AND FEEDBACK**  
We welcome your questions, comments and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue at [info@onemorelesbian.com](mailto:info@onemorelesbian.com)

**TERMS AND CONDITIONS**  
Please also visit our Terms of Use section that explains other terms and conditions governing our Site.

Effective Date: November 1, 2011
